[
    [
        {
            "question": "Work function is 4.0 eV. Longest wavelength to emit photoelectrons is:",
            "options": [
                "540 nm",
                "400 nm",
                "310 nm",
                "220 nm"
            ],
            "correctOption": "310 nm",
            "id": 39
        },
        {
            "question": "Statement I: Adding heat raises temp. Statement II: Positive work done increases volume.",
            "options": [
                "Statement I is true but Statement II is false",
                "Both Statements are true",
                "Both Statements are false",
                "Statement I is false but Statement II is true"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Statement I is false but Statement II is true",
            "id": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "For y = sin(\u03c9t) + cos(\u03c9t), the amplitude is:",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "1.414",
                "2",
                "1.5"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1.414",
            "id": 17
        },
        {
            "question": "Moment of inertia of a semicircular ring about axis through center perpendicular to plane is xMR\u00b2. Find x:",
            "options": [
                "4",
                "1",
                "6",
                "2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1",
            "id": 7
        },
        {
            "question": "Temp of gas is -78\u00b0C and avg KE is k. Temp for avg KE = 2k is:",
            "options": [
                "117",
                "320",
                "160",
                "-157"
            ],
            "correctOption": "117",
            "id": 13
        },
        {
            "question": "As the beam enters the medium, it will:",
            "options": [
                "travel as a cylindrical beam",
                "converge",
                "diverge",
                "diverge near axis and converge at periphery"
            ],
            "correctOption": "converge",
            "id": 32
        },
        {
            "question": "Red LED emits 0.1W uniformly. Electric field amplitude at 1 m is:",
            "options": [
                "2.45 V/m",
                "7.75 V/m",
                "1.73 V/m",
                "5.48 V/m"
            ],
            "correctOption": "2.45 V/m",
            "id": 43
        },
        {
            "question": "Average KE of a monatomic molecule is 0.414 eV. Temp is:",
            "options": [
                "3000 K",
                "3200 K",
                "1600 K",
                "1500 K"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3200 K",
            "id": 12
        },
        {
            "question": "The energy of a photon is 3.3 \u00d7 10\u207b\u00b9\u2079 J. Its frequency is (Planck's constant h = 6.626 \u00d7 10\u207b\u00b3\u2074 Js):",
            "options": [
                "5 \u00d7 10\u00b9\u2074 Hz",
                "3 \u00d7 10\u2078 Hz",
                "2 \u00d7 10\u00b9\u2074 Hz",
                "1 \u00d7 10\u2079 Hz"
            ],
            "correctOption": "5 \u00d7 10\u00b9\u2074 Hz",
            "id": 50
        },
        {
            "question": "A body cools from 80\u00b0C to 60\u00b0C in 5 min. Room temp is 20\u00b0C. Time to cool from 60\u00b0C to 40\u00b0C:",
            "options": [
                "500 s",
                "25 / 3 s",
                "450 s",
                "420 s"
            ],
            "correctOption": "500 s",
            "id": 11
        },
        {
            "question": "A vector of magnitude 10 units makes an angle of 60\u00b0 with the x-axis. Its y-component is:",
            "options": [
                "10\u221a3/2",
                "10/2",
                "5\u221a3",
                "5"
            ],
            "correctOption": "10\u221a3/2",
            "id": 22
        },
        {
            "question": "Two satellites A and B in same orbit. A is twice mass of B. Which is same for both?",
            "options": [
                "Potential energy",
                "Total energy",
                "Kinetic energy",
                "Speed"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Speed",
            "id": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "In an LCR series circuit, the resonance frequency is given by:",
            "options": [
                "1/(2\u03c0\u221a(LC))",
                "1/(2\u03c0RC)",
                "1/(2\u03c0LR)",
                "1/(LC)"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1/(2\u03c0\u221a(LC))",
            "id": 48
        },
        {
            "question": "Needles of ferro-, para- and diamagnetic materials react to magnet by:",
            "options": [
                "attract N1 strongly, N2 weakly and repel N3 weakly",
                "attract all three",
                "attract N1 and N2 strongly but repel N3",
                "attract N1 strongly, but repel N2 and N3 weakly"
            ],
            "correctOption": "attract N1 strongly, N2 weakly and repel N3 weakly",
            "id": 41
        },
        {
            "question": "A car accelerates uniformly from rest and covers a distance of 100 m in 5 s. Its acceleration is:",
            "options": [
                "8 m/s\u00b2",
                "10 m/s\u00b2",
                "5 m/s\u00b2",
                "6 m/s\u00b2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "8 m/s\u00b2",
            "id": 21
        },
        {
            "question": "Two projectiles A and B are thrown at 40 m/s and 60 m/s at angles 30\u00b0 and 60\u00b0. The ratio of their ranges is:",
            "options": [
                "4 : 9",
                "2 : 3",
                "1 : 1",
                "3 : 2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "4 : 9",
            "id": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Which law states that the net external torque on a system is equal to the rate of change of angular momentum?",
            "options": [
                "Newton's First Law",
                "Conservation of Angular Momentum",
                "Newton\u2019s Second Law for Rotation",
                "Kepler's Second Law"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Newton\u2019s Second Law for Rotation",
            "id": 25
        },
        {
            "question": "The dimensional formula for pressure is:",
            "options": [
                "ML\u207b\u00b9T\u207b\u00b2",
                "MLT\u207b\u00b2",
                "ML\u00b2T\u207b\u00b2",
                "M\u207b\u00b9L\u207b\u00b9T\u207b\u00b2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "ML\u207b\u00b9T\u207b\u00b2",
            "id": 23
        },
        {
            "question": "In hydrogen atom transition to ground state:",
            "options": [
                "kinetic energy decreases, potential energy increases but total remains same",
                "kinetic energy increases, potential and total decrease",
                "kinetic and total decrease, potential increases",
                "kinetic, potential and total energy decrease"
            ],
            "correctOption": "kinetic energy increases, potential and total decrease",
            "id": 37
        },
        {
            "question": "Phase difference between alternating current and emf is \u03c0/2. Not in circuit?",
            "options": [
                "LC",
                "L alone",
                "C alone",
                "R, L"
            ],
            "correctOption": "R, L",
            "id": 45
        },
        {
            "question": "Weight of a body on Earth is 400 N. At half Earth's radius depth, it will be:",
            "options": [
                "200 N",
                "300 N",
                "100 N",
                "Zero"
            ],
            "correctOption": "200 N",
            "id": 6
        },
        {
            "question": "Engine between boiling and freezing points of water. Efficiency:",
            "options": [
                "2, 3 and 4 only",
                "2 and 3 only",
                "2 and 4 only",
                "1 and 2 only"
            ],
            "correctOption": "2 and 4 only",
            "id": 14
        },
        {
            "question": "Eye is modeled as a refracting surface. Distance from surface for focus is:",
            "options": [
                "3.1 cm",
                "4.0 cm",
                "1 cm",
                "2 cm"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3.1 cm",
            "id": 33
        },
        {
            "question": "Radioactive source gives 1600 cps at t=0, 100 cps at t=8s. At t=6s it gives:",
            "options": [
                "250",
                "360",
                "150",
                "200"
            ],
            "correctOption": "200",
            "id": 40
        },
        {
            "question": "A radioactive substance has a half-life of 10 days. In how many days will only 1/8th of the substance remain?",
            "options": [
                "30",
                "20",
                "40",
                "10"
            ],
            "correctOption": "30",
            "id": 49
        },
        {
            "question": "A solid conducting sphere with charge Q is surrounded by an uncharged conducting hollow shell. If shell is given charge \u20134Q, the new potential difference is:",
            "options": [
                "4 V",
                "V",
                "2 V",
                "\u20132 V"
            ],
            "correctOption": "V",
            "id": 27
        },
        {
            "question": "In SHM, if displacement is half amplitude, ratio of PE to KE is:",
            "options": [
                "1:1",
                "1:4",
                "2:1",
                "1:3"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1:3",
            "id": 20
        },
        {
            "question": "Two equal resistances in series consume 60 W. When in parallel, the power consumed is:",
            "options": [
                "240 W",
                "120 W",
                "60 W",
                "30 W"
            ],
            "correctOption": "240 W",
            "id": 28
        },
        {
            "question": "Four particles A, B, C, D have same momentum. Which has max kinetic energy?",
            "options": [
                "D",
                "C",
                "A",
                "B"
            ],
            "correctOption": "A",
            "id": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "Fundamental frequency of a closed pipe = first overtone of open pipe. If open pipe is 60 cm, closed pipe is:",
            "options": [
                "15",
                "20",
                "25",
                "60"
            ],
            "correctOption": "15",
            "id": 16
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "The higher oxidation states are more stable down the group among transition elements unlike p-block elements. Copper cannot liberate hydrogen from weak acids.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
            "id": 8
        },
        {
            "question": "The molecular formula of second homologue in the mono carboxylic acids series is:",
            "options": [
                "C2H2O4",
                "C2H2O2",
                "CH2O",
                "C3H6O2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "C2H2O4",
            "id": 18
        },
        {
            "question": "The incorrect statements regarding enzymes are:",
            "options": [
                "Enzymes are bio catalysts.",
                "Enzymes are non-specific and cannot catalyse different kinds of reactions.",
                "Most enzymes are globular proteins.",
                "Enzyme - oxidase catalyses the hydrolysis of maltose into glucose."
            ],
            "correctOption": "Enzyme - oxidase catalyses the hydrolysis of maltose into glucose.",
            "id": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "The reaction at cathode in the cells commonly used in clocks involves:",
            "options": [
                "reduction of Mn from +4 to +3",
                "oxidation of Mn from +2 to +7",
                "oxidation of Mn from +3 to +4",
                "reduction of Mn from +7 to +2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "reduction of Mn from +4 to +3",
            "id": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "The IUPAC name of CH3CHO is",
            "options": [
                "Acetaldehyde",
                "Ethanal",
                "Methyl aldehyde",
                "Ethanol"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Ethanal",
            "id": 22
        },
        {
            "question": "The element having the highest first ionization enthalpy is",
            "options": [
                "C",
                "Al",
                "N",
                "Si"
            ],
            "correctOption": "N",
            "id": 39
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one of the following substances has the highest proton affinity?",
            "options": [
                "H2S",
                "NH3",
                "PH3",
                "H2O"
            ],
            "correctOption": "NH3",
            "id": 32
        },
        {
            "question": "N(CH3)3 and P(CH3)3 can act as ligands. As N and P are from same group, the nature of bonding is always same with transition metals.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
            "id": 9
        },
        {
            "question": "High concentration of strong nucleophilic reagent with secondary alkyl halides will follow SN2 mechanism. Secondary alkyl halide with excess ethanol follows SN1 mechanism.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
            "id": 13
        },
        {
            "question": "The metal that cannot be obtained by electrolysis of an aqueous solution of its salt is",
            "options": [
                "Cr",
                "Ca",
                "Ag",
                "Cu"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Ca",
            "id": 27
        },
        {
            "question": "Which nitrogen compound does not give Lassaigne's test?",
            "options": [
                "Hydrazine",
                "Urea",
                "Glycene",
                "Phenyl Hydrazine"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Hydrazine",
            "id": 16
        },
        {
            "question": "The process with negative entropy change is",
            "options": [
                "dissolution of iodine in water",
                "sublimation of dry ice",
                "synthesis of ammonia from N2 and H2",
                "dissociation of CaSO4(s) to CaO(s) and SO3(g)"
            ],
            "correctOption": "synthesis of ammonia from N2 and H2",
            "id": 34
        },
        {
            "question": "Common name of Benzene - 1,2 - diol is:",
            "options": [
                "o-cresol",
                "catechol",
                "quinol",
                "resorcinol"
            ],
            "correctOption": "catechol",
            "id": 12
        },
        {
            "question": "The IUPAC name of CH3COCH(CH3)2 is",
            "options": [
                "3-methyl-2-butanone",
                "2-methyl-3-butanone",
                "4-methylisopropyl ketone",
                "Isopropylmethyl ketone"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3-methyl-2-butanone",
            "id": 21
        },
        {
            "question": "The shape of carbocation is:",
            "options": [
                "trigonal planar",
                "tetrahedral",
                "diagonal",
                "linear"
            ],
            "correctOption": "trigonal planar",
            "id": 36
        },
        {
            "question": "The gas liberated by the electrolysis of Dipotassium succinate solution is:",
            "options": [
                "Ethyne",
                "Propene",
                "Ethane",
                "Ethene"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Ethene",
            "id": 25
        },
        {
            "question": "Addition of phosphate fertilizers to water bodies causes",
            "options": [
                "enhanced growth of algae",
                "increase in amount of dissolved oxygen in water",
                "deposition of calcium phosphate",
                "increase in fish population"
            ],
            "correctOption": "enhanced growth of algae",
            "id": 28
        },
        {
            "question": "Statement I: Fluorine has most negative electron gain enthalpy in its group. Statement II: Oxygen has least negative electron gain enthalpy in its group.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE",
            "id": 40
        },
        {
            "question": "Determine the total number of neutrons in three isotopes of hydrogen",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "2",
                "3",
                "4"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3",
            "id": 29
        },
        {
            "question": "The vapor pressure of pure benzene and methyl benzene at 27\u00b0C is given as 80 Torr and 24 Torr, respectively. The mole fraction of methyl benzene in vapor phase, in equilibrium with an equimolar mixture of those two liquids is:",
            "options": [
                "0.23",
                "0.89",
                "0.99",
                "0.73"
            ],
            "correctOption": "0.23",
            "id": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Chlorine water on standing loses its colour and forms:",
            "options": [
                "HCl and HClO2",
                "HCl only",
                "HOCl and HOCl2",
                "HCl and HOCl"
            ],
            "correctOption": "HCl and HOCl",
            "id": 30
        },
        {
            "question": "Haloalkanes react with KCN to form alkyl cyanides, but with AgCN form isocyanides. KCN and AgCN are highly ionic compounds.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
            "id": 14
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the volume of 1 g of H2 gas in litres at N.T.P",
            "options": [
                "11.2",
                "22.4",
                "2.24",
                "112"
            ],
            "correctOption": "11.2",
            "id": 31
        },
        {
            "question": "At constant temperature, a gas is at a pressure of 940.3 mm Hg. The pressure at which its volume decreases by 40% is __________ mm Hg.",
            "options": [
                "1567",
                "1600",
                "2000",
                "3527"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1567",
            "id": 38
        },
        {
            "question": "\u2206U is equal to",
            "options": [
                "adiabatic work",
                "isothermal work",
                "isochoric work",
                "isobaric work"
            ],
            "correctOption": "adiabatic work",
            "id": 33
        },
        {
            "question": "Acidity of \u03b1-hydrogens of aldehydes and ketones is responsible for Aldol reaction. Benzaldehyde and ethanal will not give Cross-Aldol product.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE",
            "id": 19
        },
        {
            "question": "The incorrect postulates of the Dalton's atomic theory are:",
            "options": [
                "Atoms of different elements differ in mass.",
                "Matter consists of divisible atoms.",
                "Compounds are formed when atoms of different element combine in a fixed ratio.",
                "Chemical reactions involve reorganisation of atoms."
            ],
            "correctOption": "Matter consists of divisible atoms.",
            "id": 37
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one of the following conformation of cyclohexane is chiral?",
            "options": [
                "Twist boat",
                "Rigid",
                "Chair",
                "Boat"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Twist boat",
            "id": 23
        },
        {
            "question": "Phenol treated with chloroform in presence of sodium hydroxide, then hydrolyzed in acid results in:",
            "options": [
                "2-Hydroxybenzaldehyde",
                "Salicylic Acid",
                "quinol",
                "Benzene-1,2-diol"
            ],
            "correctOption": "2-Hydroxybenzaldehyde",
            "id": 11
        },
        {
            "question": "Kjeldahl method is applicable to pyridine. The nitrogen in pyridine can be converted to ammonium sulfate.",
            "options": [
                "BOTH I AND II ARE TRUE",
                "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
                "II IS TRUE BUT I IS FALSE",
                "I IS TRUE BUT II IS FALSE"
            ],
            "correctOption": "BOTH I AND II ARE FALSE",
            "id": 17
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "question": "In an increasing geometric progression... the sum of the 4th, 6th and 8th terms is equal to:",
            "options": [
                "45",
                "91",
                "76",
                "50"
            ],
            "correctOption": "91",
            "id": 42
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of relations... which are reflexive and transitive but not symmetric, is __________.",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "2",
                "3",
                "5"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3",
            "id": 24
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of sin(0\u00c2\u00b0)?",
            "options": [
                "0",
                "1",
                "-1",
                "0.5"
            ],
            "correctOption": "0",
            "id": 17
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of solutions of sin3x = cos 2x, in the interval (90,180) is :",
            "options": [
                "4",
                "7",
                "3",
                "1"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1",
            "id": 55
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the integral of cos(x) dx?",
            "options": [
                "sin(x) + C",
                "-cos(x) + C",
                "-sin(x) + C",
                "cos(x) + C"
            ],
            "correctOption": "sin(x) + C",
            "id": 20
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of log10(100)?",
            "options": [
                "2",
                "1",
                "10",
                "100"
            ],
            "correctOption": "2",
            "id": 6
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the solution to the equation x^2 - 4 = 0?",
            "options": [
                "x = \u00c2\u00b12",
                "x = 2",
                "x = -2",
                "x = 0"
            ],
            "correctOption": "x = \u00c2\u00b12",
            "id": 18
        },
        {
            "question": "A circle is inscribed in an equilateral triangle of side of length 12... then m+n^2 is equal to",
            "options": [
                "900",
                "470",
                "408",
                "488"
            ],
            "correctOption": "408",
            "id": 59
        },
        {
            "question": "A variable line L passes through the point (3,5)... The minimum area of the triangle OAB , where O is the origin, is",
            "options": [
                "30",
                "23",
                "35",
                "43"
            ],
            "correctOption": "30",
            "id": 56
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the area of a circle with radius r?",
            "options": [
                "\u00cf\u20acr^2",
                "2\u00cf\u20acr",
                "\u00cf\u20acr",
                "r^2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "\u00cf\u20acr^2",
            "id": 11
        },
        {
            "question": "In a survey of 220 students... m and n respectively be the least and the most number of students who studied all the three subjects. Then m+n is equal to ___________.",
            "options": [
                "45",
                "20",
                "35",
                "50"
            ],
            "correctOption": "45",
            "id": 41
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the slope of the line y = 3x + 2?",
            "options": [
                "3",
                "2",
                "-3",
                "-2"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3",
            "id": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "a = sin36 is a root of which of the following equation?",
            "options": [
                "16x^4-20x^2+5=0",
                "16x^4+20x^2+5=0",
                "16x^4-20x^2-5=0",
                "16x^4+20x^2-5=0"
            ],
            "correctOption": "16x^4-20x^2+5=0",
            "id": 31
        },
        {
            "question": "A software company sets up m number of computer systems... then it took 8 more days to finish the assignment. The value of m is equal to:",
            "options": [
                "150",
                "220",
                "135",
                "250"
            ],
            "correctOption": "150",
            "id": 23
        },
        {
            "question": "The portion of the line 4x+5y=20 in the first quadrant is trisected by the lines P and Q passing through the origin. The tangent of an angle between the lines P and Q is :",
            "options": [
                "45",
                "30/41",
                "35/41",
                "43/7"
            ],
            "correctOption": "30/41",
            "id": 37
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of cos(0\u00c2\u00b0)?",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "0",
                "-1",
                "0.5"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1",
            "id": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of e^0?",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "0",
                "e",
                "-1"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1",
            "id": 9
        },
        {
            "question": "A software company sets up m number of computer systems... then it took 8 more days to finish the assignment. The value of m is equal to:",
            "options": [
                "150",
                "220",
                "135",
                "250"
            ],
            "correctOption": "150",
            "id": 43
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of 3-digit numbers... not divisible by 3 , is equal to ________.",
            "options": [
                "36",
                "37",
                "35",
                "43"
            ],
            "correctOption": "36",
            "id": 28
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of solutions of sin3x = cos 2x, in the interval (90,180) is :",
            "options": [
                "4",
                "7",
                "3",
                "1"
            ],
            "correctOption": "1",
            "id": 35
        },
        {
            "question": "If the x-intercept of a focal chord of the parabola y^2=8x+4y+4 is 3, then the length of this chord is equal to ____________.",
            "options": [
                "42",
                "72",
                "36",
                "16"
            ],
            "correctOption": "16",
            "id": 40
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of solutions of the equation x + 2tanx = \u03c0/2 in the interval [0, 2\u03c0] is :",
            "options": [
                "9",
                "7",
                "3",
                "4"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3",
            "id": 34
        },
        {
            "question": "If z = x + iy satisfies |z| - 2 = 0 and |z - i| - |z + 5i| = 0, then :",
            "options": [
                "x+2y+4=0",
                "x+2y-4=0",
                "x-2y+4=0",
                "x-2y-4=0"
            ],
            "correctOption": "x+2y+4=0",
            "id": 46
        },
        {
            "question": "The equation y = sinx sin (x + 2) \u2013 sin^2 (x + 1) represents a straight line lying in :",
            "options": [
                "III and IV QUADRANTS",
                "II and IV QUADRANTS",
                "I, III and IV QUADRANTS",
                "II,III and IV QUADRANTS"
            ],
            "correctOption": "III and IV QUADRANTS",
            "id": 53
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of relations... which are reflexive and transitive but not symmetric, is __________.",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "2",
                "3",
                "5"
            ],
            "correctOption": "3",
            "id": 44
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the quadratic formula?",
            "options": [
                "x = (-b \u00c2\u00b1 \u00e2\u02c6\u0161(b\u00c2\u00b2 - 4ac)) / 2a",
                "x = (b \u00c2\u00b1 \u00e2\u02c6\u0161(b\u00c2\u00b2 - 4ac)) / 2a",
                "x = (-b \u00c2\u00b1 \u00e2\u02c6\u0161(b\u00c2\u00b2 + 4ac)) / 2a",
                "x = (b \u00c2\u00b1 \u00e2\u02c6\u0161(b\u00c2\u00b2 + 4ac)) / 2a"
            ],
            "correctOption": "x = (-b \u00c2\u00b1 \u00e2\u02c6\u0161(b\u00c2\u00b2 - 4ac)) / 2a",
            "id": 8
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the volume of a sphere with radius r?",
            "options": [
                "(4/3)\u00cf\u20acr^3",
                "2\u00cf\u20acr^3",
                "\u00cf\u20acr^3",
                "(3/4)\u00cf\u20acr^3"
            ],
            "correctOption": "(4/3)\u00cf\u20acr^3",
            "id": 12
        },
        {
            "question": "a = sin36 is a root of which of the following equation?",
            "options": [
                "16x^4-20x^2+5=0",
                "16x^4+20x^2+5=0",
                "16x^4-20x^2-5=0",
                "16x^4+20x^2-5=0"
            ],
            "correctOption": "16x^4-20x^2+5=0",
            "id": 51
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of 3-digit numbers... not divisible by 3 , is equal to ________.",
            "options": [
                "36",
                "37",
                "35",
                "43"
            ],
            "correctOption": "36",
            "id": 48
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the solution to the equation 2x + 3 = 7?",
            "options": [
                "x = 2",
                "x = 3",
                "x = 4",
                "x = 1"
            ],
            "correctOption": "x = 2",
            "id": 5
        }
    ]
]